<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MOS-MOS To The MOON</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>MOSDAO</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 10:32:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/MOS-72px.png</url>
	<title>MOS-MOS To The MOON</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>MOS Asia Pacific node representative visits the ambassador of the Federated States of Micronesia in China</title>
		<link>/mos-asia-pacific-node-representative-visits-the-ambassador-of-the-federated-states-of-micronesia-in-china/</link>
				<comments>/mos-asia-pacific-node-representative-visits-the-ambassador-of-the-federated-states-of-micronesia-in-china/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 10:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[NEWS]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=630</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p><img class="alignnone size-medium" src="http://www.mosdao.io/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/photo_2019-09-27_09-13-52.jpg" width="1280" height="852" /></p>
<p>On the afternoon of September 28th, Mr. Thomas, the representative of the MOS Asia Pacific node, visited the Embassy of the Federated States of Micronesia (hereinafter referred to as the “Federal Union”) in Beijing. Ambassador Carlson D. Apis, Ambassador of the Federal Embassy in China, met with Mr. Thomas and his party. The two sides held talks on promoting MOS and Micronesia blockchain financial infrastructure.</p>
<p>At the symposium, Lord Carl Appis expressed his gratitude to the MOS team for providing the opportunity to provide blockchain technical training to the students of the Federal Republic. He said: &#8220;I have been paying attention to the blockchain field for 2 years. Blockchain technology is an Internet-based distributed ledger technology with decentralization, high security, low credit cost, inability to tamper with and transparency. It provides a new credit creation mechanism and has broad application prospects in the financial field. The secret federation attaches great importance to blockchain technology. We believe that the blockchain will not even have a subversive effect on the financial industry. Bring a huge impact.&#8221;</p>
<p>His Excellency Carl Appis gave a positive assessment of MOS&#8217;s contribution to the financial industry. The Federal Embassy in China will fully support the MOS project and cooperate with Micronesia and Micronesia. Lord Carl Apis pointed out that Micronesia College is the only university in the United States, shouldering the heavy responsibility of cultivating national talents and supporting the development of national industries. MOS is the builder of global financial infrastructure. And sincerely invite the MOS team to visit Micronesia.</p>
<p>Mr. Thomas, the representative of the MOS Asia Pacific node, thanked Carl Apis for his active matchmaking and promoted the cooperation between MOS and Micronesia. He said that MOS is a new generation of blockchain financial infrastructure based on DAO2.0. It is recommended that both parties can cooperate as soon as possible, and sincerely invites Lord Carl Apis and the President of Micronesia to visit MOS to learn about The situation of disciplines and industrial development is conducive to enhancing mutual understanding and solidifying the foundation of cooperation.</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>/mos-asia-pacific-node-representative-visits-the-ambassador-of-the-federated-states-of-micronesia-in-china/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Technical evaluation of high-quality blockchain projects -MOS</title>
		<link>/technical-evaluation-of-high-quality-blockchain-projects-mos/</link>
				<comments>/technical-evaluation-of-high-quality-blockchain-projects-mos/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 10:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Media report]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=627</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p><img class="size-medium aligncenter" src="http://www.mosdao.io/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/MOS-72px_wps%E5%9B%BE%E7%89%87.png" width="72" height="72" /></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> Name: MOS Morse</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Token symbol: MOS</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Total tokens: 2.1 billion MOS tokens</p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Initial release: 110 million</p>
<p>MOS Moss Project&#8211;Decentralized Self-Organizing Financial Services Operating System Based on DAO, a great technological innovation, DAO2.0, was developed. The MOS project was hailed as a phenomenon of unicorns in the blockchain of 2019. Level project.</p>
<p>The MOS Moss project includes MOS tokens, MOSDAO Morse Council, MOS Global Public Chain, MOSPOOL Morse Mine Pool, MOSOTC Eco, MOSEX Moss Digital Currency Exchange, MOSITO Morse Internet of Things and other rich applications.</p>
<p>MOS tokens are equity tokens that link all MOS Moss project eco-products. Like Bitcoin BTC, MOS token issuance is all decentralized through smart contracts, and no one can change the circulation. Because of the limited number of releases, it has the same huge value-added space as Bitcoin. MOS tokens are tokens under the new digital currency 3.0 concept. It can not only be a low-cost and fast global payment like Bitcoin, but also has the function of equity vouchers. With MOS tokens, you can enjoy the profit sharing of all financial products sold by MOS Digital Finance and MOSDAO (Moss Parliament). Under the value-added attribute that MOS tokens can not be over-extended, the value-added attribute of equity voucher dividends is increased. This makes MOS tokens more investment value.</p>
<p><strong>Blockchain advantage</strong></p>
<p>Because the MOS project is doing blockchain financial services, the MOS Moss team has built a comprehensive MOS Moss based on its many years of advantages in the financial field. The MOSDAO Morse Council is the decentralization of the MOS Morse Ecology. Organize super-applications, rely on MOS Moss to centralize the underlying technology to build a scientific, fair and transparent financial platform for asset appreciation and secondary distribution of wealth, leading the project partners and investors of the blockchain ecosystem, letting capital be all MOS coin holder services provide an orderly accumulation and appreciation of assets that are responsive to economic trends.</p>
<p><strong>Roadmap aspect</strong></p>
<p>In 2018, MOS officially established the decentralized community financial reform and promotion team, recruiting the world&#8217;s professional and well-known industry people to explore together based on the decentralized financial concept, forming a prototype of the application of decentralized finance to the MOSDAO Morse Council.</p>
<p>After nearly a year of exploration and research and development, the MOS Moss project first proposed the social experiment feasibility report of DAO2.0 in the world blockchain conference in 2019. The research mainly clarified why DAO is currently The infrastructure needs to face a wider audience to make further changes and DAO2.0&#8217;s major blockchain technology breakthrough has received a general consensus from the industry.</p>
<h4><strong>Team aspect</strong></h4>
<p>It is reported that the MOS Moss project is composed of a team of 38 people and a consultant of 7 people. Let&#8217;s take a look at it.</p>
<p>Andy Chia CEO</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-medium" src="http://www.mosdao.io/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/%E5%9B%BE%E7%89%872_meitu_1.jpg" width="792" height="783" /></p>
<p>CFAGraduated from the National University of Singapore and Washington University in St. Louis, a member of the Singapore Blockchain Reform Standards Committee, one of the early investors and evangelists in Ethereum, has participated in early investments in a number of outstanding projects around the world, such as XRP, SC , NEO, ATOM, etc.; have more than 10 years of investment banking, global marketing and trading experience before starting MOS.</p>
<p>Yeow Lim COO</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-medium" src="http://www.mosdao.io/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/%E5%9B%BE%E7%89%873_meitu_2.jpg" width="602" height="604" /></p>
<p>Graduated from Nanyang Technological University, he joined the blockchain industry in 2014. He is a continuous entrepreneur in the blockchain industry. He has extensive experience in project operation and promotion. He has assisted many Singapore blockchain companies in financing (more than 10 million US dollars). Yeow has in-depth research on the underlying technology of blockchain and blockchain finance, and is committed to the optimization of next-generation blockchain infrastructure construction and social collaboration systems.</p>
<p>Deacon W  Technical director</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-medium" src="http://www.mosdao.io/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/%E5%9B%BE%E7%89%874.png" width="739" height="757" /></p>
<p>Graduated from Lancaster University, UK, a member of the Bitcoin Free Community, has long been committed to the design of incentive mechanism and optimization of encryption algorithm based on game theory. Former NOKIA system architect, and has worked in many well-known companies such as IB, FundingClub, and as a technical leader involved in the development of digital currency exchanges and wallets, with more than 7 years of experience in distributed system development.</p>
<p>In addition to the elite management team, the MOS Moss project also has a strong technical team consisting of the industry&#8217;s top computer algorithm talents and blockchain technology elites. The entire team brings together elites in the financial and technical fields to become a strong endorsement of the project!</p>
<p><strong>Technological innovation</strong></p>
<p>The super-application MOSDAO Morse Council under the MOS project first realized the breakthrough of the MOS project feature technology.</p>
<p>Because the MOS project designed a new organizational structure (ie, commissioned underwriting) that includes token issuers, underwriting nodes, sub-underwriting nodes, and other roles, these roles are interrelated and mutually motivated by distributed rules, effectively avoiding The traditional primary market project side platform people have purified the market environment for the possibility of evil.</p>
<p>In the DAO 2.0 architecture of the MOS project, in order to solve the decentralization problem in the impossible triangle, a random mechanism based on VRF (Verifiable Random Function) is adopted, that is, each time a topic, project, and voting are decided. In the process of adding certain random factors, avoiding the reliance on specific members and the possibility of stakeholders paying bribes to known members, truly achieve &#8220;decentralization.&#8221;</p>
<p>The development of a decentralized organization is inseparable from the support of the nodes, which requires corresponding rewards for their contributions. In the past DAO 1.0 project, it relied only on a single mechanism such as workload (PoW), equity (PoS), etc., which limited the flexibility of various applications derived from the organization. Therefore, in the MOS project, Chuangw Xindi adopted a consensus mechanism called Poof (Proof of Finance Contribution), which for the first time combines two different types of incentives in the form of weights: this greatly improves The flexibility and expandability of the applications derived from the MOS project.</p>
<p>Members and investors, in assessing the development prospects of each project, used to rely on their own experience, resulting in a lot of uncertainty and risk. To this end, the MOS project uses the Endogenous Growth Theory (EGT) established by Nobel Prize-winning economist Paul Romer to analyze the future trends and growth rates of each project. The parameters used include the number of tokens of the project, the number of nodes, and the development investment. After the EGT-based empirical formula is transformed, the quantitative growth curve of each project is obtained, which greatly reduces the members and investors when selecting the project. Blindness.</p>
<p>The MOS project, which is mainly for various financial applications, provides a set of “DAF” (Decentralized Autonomous Finance) protocol groups for various application projects, and has developed the corresponding MOSDAO DAPP. In this way, project parties can easily use these protocols and infrastructure to develop application scenarios and services that they and their members need.</p>
<p>MOS project will rely on careful architecture design, advanced technology, careful logic setting, strong intelligent contract support and unique cross-chain and sidechain technology to meet the needs of various financial industry applications and derivatives. Service industry preferred</p>
<p>MOSDAO Morse Council will be more suitable for market demand, with the more advanced DAO2.0 concept and optimized organizational structure to become the most efficient token issuance application in blockchain finance.</p>
<p><strong>Landing application and market analysis</strong></p>
<p>The MOS Moss project is a blockchain-based integration of decentralized finance and distributed Internet research, and will provide a one-stop, all-round financial service. MOS Moss includes MOS tokens, MOSDAO Morse Council, MOS Global Public Chain, MOSPOOL Morse Mine Pool, MOSOTC Eco, MOSEX Moss Digital Currency Exchange, MOSITO Morse Internet of Things and other rich applications. MOS&#8217;s vision is to enable humans to equally obtain the autonomy of financial services, jointly build and build incentives that meet the needs of members of the community and provide incentives, while becoming a new generation of distributed independent of a single “central” organization. Autonomous organization. At present, it has reached a blockchain strategic cooperation agreement with six countries to help the six countries gradually break the traditional financial barriers by means of distributed cooperation and relying on blockchain technology (DAO2.0).</p>
<p><strong>Impact on the original industry</strong></p>
<p>The technological breakthrough of the MOS Moss project can provide efficient service and support for government and commercial projects, and promote and apply blockchain technology to a wider range of fields, providing new production power for the real economy and empowering the traditional economy.</p>
<p>The digital asset allocation function provided by MOSDAO Morse Council will be based on the theory and method of asset allocation. The main body of the configuration will be transferred from traditional financial products to encrypted digital assets based on blockchain technology. Ordinary investors can purchase these configuration combination blockchain products to achieve personal digital wealth appreciation.</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>/technical-evaluation-of-high-quality-blockchain-projects-mos/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>MOS Starlight plans to enter the Embassy of Nigeria</title>
		<link>/mos-starlight-plans-to-enter-the-embassy-of-nigeria/</link>
				<comments>/mos-starlight-plans-to-enter-the-embassy-of-nigeria/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 10:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[NEWS]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=623</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p><img class="alignnone size-medium" src="http://www.mosdao.io/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/photo_2019-10-09_16-08-29-1.jpg" width="1280" height="853" /></p>
<p>Recently, MOS Asia Pacific node representative Mr. Thomas visited Ahmad Jidda, Ambassador of the Embassy of Nigeria to China, on the theme of “Leading new ideas in blockchain technology and collaborating on new financial ecology”. Blockchain financial technology has been discussed in depth in a series of issues such as banking applications and technological innovations. Ahmad Jidda, the ambassador to China, expressed his strong interest in the MOS project. Optimistic about the future development of the MOS project, affirming the direction of the MOS project in the blockchain finance field, the future may bring more opportunities for cooperation and development opportunities for both parties.</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>/mos-starlight-plans-to-enter-the-embassy-of-nigeria/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>How will MOS come to the future?</title>
		<link>/how-will-mos-come-to-the-future/</link>
				<comments>/how-will-mos-come-to-the-future/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 09:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Media report]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=614</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p>In the recent currency shocks, mainstream currencies plummeted overnight, and the secondary market was raging, and the quantum hegemony that threatened the security of Bitcoin private keys was rampant. The highly-recognized “rich second-generation” exchange Bakkt went online after trading. The volume was so bad. The news caused the market to panic, whether the encrypted digital currency has reached the bear market cycle? Can there be strength projects to turn the tide?</p>
<p>In the downturn of the market, the innovative project MOS Moss broke through the turmoil and sprung up. It took the DAO 2.0 concept and the innovative economic model to seize the opportunity. It was regarded by the industry as the next new ecological market, and the MOS project became the model. Inciting capital leverage?</p>
<p><img class="alignnone size-medium" src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/图片5_meitu_1.jpg" width="1600" height="995" /></p>
<p>MOS project breaks homogenization and eliminates the sudden rise and fall of tokens.</p>
<p>At present, the currency project is highly homogenized and lacks a healthy mode of operation. Many project coins cannot escape the short-lived fate of the survival cycle. Usually, after two or three price fluctuations, there will be long-term sideways, and then it will start to fall. The project side will not be able to return to the sky at this time, because in the continuous decline of the currency price, investors will adjust their expectations, and most of them only seek back. It will not be bargain-hunt. At this time, as long as the project side pulls the plate, the plate will appear. The biggest village will turn to the amaranth by the project side, and the collective trampling panic will even lead to the zero price of the currency. The blockchain project has long been stuck in this infinite loop, with serious homogenization and no healthy model.</p>
<p>The MOS project is a decentralized self-organizing financial services operating system based on DAO based on a great technological innovation called DAO2.0. The MOS project uses the DAO 2.0 concept and a highly competitive and differentiated economic model to break the homogenization of the currency project. It advocates the community consensus to determine the value of the token, avoiding the centralization operation and causing the currency price to plummet. Become a dark horse in the industry!</p>
<p>The MOS project has designed a new organizational structure (ie, commissioned underwriting) that includes token issuers, underwriting nodes, sub-underwriting nodes, and other roles. These roles are interrelated and mutually motivated by distributed rules, effectively avoiding tradition. The market leader of the primary market project has purified the market environment for the possibility of evil in the interests of the people.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>In the DAO 2.0 architecture of the MOS project, in order to solve the decentralization problem in the impossible triangle, a random mechanism based on VRF (Verifiable Random Function) is adopted, that is, each time a topic, project, and voting are decided. In the process of adding certain random factors, avoiding the reliance on specific members and the possibility of stakeholders paying bribes to known members, truly achieve &#8220;decentralization.&#8221;</p>
<p>The development of a decentralized organization is inseparable from the support of the nodes, which requires corresponding rewards for their contributions. In the past DAO 1.0 project, it relied only on a single mechanism such as workload (PoW), equity (PoS), etc., which limited the flexibility of various applications derived from the organization. Therefore, in the MOS project, a consensus mechanism called PoFC (Proof of Finance Contribution) was innovatively adopted. For the first time, two different types of incentives were combined in the form of weights: this greatly improved Flexibility and scalability of applications derived from MOS projects.</p>
<p>Members and investors, in assessing the development prospects of each project, used to rely on their own experience, resulting in a lot of uncertainty and risk. To this end, the MOS project uses the Endogenous Growth Theory (EGT) established by 2018 Nobel Prize winner in economics, Paul Roemer, to analyze the future trends and growth rates of each project. The parameters used include the number of tokens of the project, the number of nodes, and the development investment. After the EGT-based empirical formula is transformed, the quantitative growth curve of each project is obtained, which greatly reduces the members and investors when selecting the project. Blindness.</p>
<p>The MOS project, which is mainly for various financial applications, provides a set of “DAF” (Decentralized Autonomous Finance) protocol groups for various application projects, and has developed the corresponding MOSDAO APP. In this way, project parties can easily use these protocols and infrastructure to develop application scenarios and services that they and their members need.</p>
<p>MOS project will rely on careful architecture design, advanced technology, careful logic setting, strong intelligent contract support and unique cross-chain and sidechain technology to meet the needs of various financial industry applications and derivatives. The first choice for the service industry.</p>
<p>In terms of the single mechanism relative to other projects, the MOS project has created a healthy and benign eco-coin loop, and the project tokens will not go to an uncontrollable abyss.</p>
<p>A new benchmark for digital currency value &#8211; MOS coins</p>
<p><strong>1.The huge advantage of the entrusted underwriting mechanism benefited by the three parties</strong></p>
<p>Before the traditional blockchain project tokens are purchased in the secondary market, they will be pre-sold in the primary market for angel round financing. Generally, they are sold by influential community leaders in the industry, but there are many community leaders running. Road, the phenomenon of investor rights protection occurs.</p>
<p>MOS coins are sold in the world&#8217;s first DAO tokens, and follow the MOS project to provide a commissioned underwriting mechanism to effectively reward project contributors under the interests of the three parties and provide reasonable solutions for token sales.</p>
<p>The token issuer issues tokens at the MOSDAO Morse Council, so there is no need to worry about the sales of the project tokens. The tokens are sold by the highly influential core underwriting nodes that have been evaluated, and the sub-underwriting nodes are professionally subject to the core underwriting nodes. With the help of investment ability, there is no need to worry about the project side running in the project selection, and the loss of the lock and other factors will cause huge property losses. From this point of view, the issuer of each token only needs to focus on the issue of token value enhancement, so that the project can grow rapidly; the core underwriting node not only expands its brand influence in the process of selling tokens, You can also enjoy the rewards of the mechanism; the sub-underwriting node can quickly identify high-quality projects, and greatly reduce the investment risk and achieve the return on investment!</p>
<p><strong>2.MOS coins use the mechanism of the release</strong></p>
<p>At present, many project tokens will be partially locked, which is undoubtedly a disguised scam, because most of the early period of token issuance is steadily rising, and even the previous currency price is likely to reach the highest point of the currency in the whole period. Locking the warehouse will bring potential losses to investors.</p>
<p>MOS coins will be opened on the exchange of DAO on the MODSAO Moss parliament. At the same time, the principal and interest will not lock the position, and the token trading will be unimpeded and the interests of investors will be guaranteed.</p>
<p><strong>3.MOS tokens use the hierarchy and thousands of deflationary rising mechanism</strong></p>
<p>Most of the projects in the industry have short life cycles, and investors are accustomed to the mentality of holding short-term investments. When the price of the currency falls, the collective panic is no matter how the project pulls, and the currency circle is only strong. MOS Moss pioneered &#8220;hierarchy&#8221;</p>
<p>And the thousand-fold deflationary rise mechanism&#8221; and the rising mechanism is constrained by smart contracts, others can not tamper with, and truly maintain the long-term stable upward trend of the project MOS tokens.</p>
<p>The initial issue price of MOS: MOS token and USDT initial exchange ratio is 10000USDT/14000MOS</p>
<p>Currency price appreciation rules: MOS adopts the “hierarchy” growth and issuance mechanism, and each 75 million tokens is set to one stage, and the initial DAO issuance pool of 75 million tokens is the first order of issuance. In the first stage, 7.5 million tokens were set as one floor. For each layer sold, the price of coins increased by 0.00143USDT. From the second stage, the number of tokens set on each floor is ten times deflated, and the value of each floor price change is unchanged at 0.00143USDT. For example: After the sales of 75 million tokens in the initial release pool of DAO in the first stage, each 7500 tokens (7.5 million/10) is set to one floor, and the price per layer increases by 0.00143USDT. The post-release phase rules are analogous. In this way, the tokens in a steadily rising trend avoid the shortcomings of the short-lived ups and downs of the small-currency, and the more they buy, the more they earn, the better the investors who give back to the early support projects.</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>/how-will-mos-come-to-the-future/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>MOS Starlight plans to enter the Embassy of Malta</title>
		<link>/mos-starlight-plans-to-enter-the-embassy-of-malta/</link>
				<comments>/mos-starlight-plans-to-enter-the-embassy-of-malta/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 08:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[NEWS]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=611</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p><img class="alignnone size-medium" src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/photo_2019-09-27_09-19-38.jpg" width="1280" height="852" /></p>
<p>Mr. Thomas, the representative of the MOS Asia Pacific node, had a cordial talk with the Ambassador of the Republic of Malta to China, Mr. John Aquilina, and made an in-depth study on the “global blockchain financial self-organizing ecosystem”. Mr. John Aquilina confirmed He also praised the MOS project&#8217;s professionalism and achievements in the blockchain finance field, and also comprehensively introduced the advantages of Malta. Malta is the first country to issue clear legislation and guidelines for the industry, taking the lead in the regulation of cryptocurrency and blockchain technology. The habitat of the world&#8217;s leading financial companies. Mr. Thomas, through the MOS Asia Pacific node representative, expressed his sincere sincerity to Malta for the MOS project. Mr. Thomas also strongly agrees: &#8220;The MOS project is simultaneously connecting with countries with multiple blockchain financial technologies open to the world. From the standpoint of cryptocurrency and financial technology, Malta is very advanced. I will convey this to the MOS team. The MOS team was impressed with the clear and forward-thinking thinking of the future.</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>/mos-starlight-plans-to-enter-the-embassy-of-malta/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
