<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>NEWS &#8211; MOS-MOS To The MOON</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>MOSDAO</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 10:32:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/MOS-72px.png</url>
	<title>NEWS &#8211; MOS-MOS To The MOON</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>MOS Asia Pacific node representative visits the ambassador of the Federated States of Micronesia in China</title>
		<link>/mos-asia-pacific-node-representative-visits-the-ambassador-of-the-federated-states-of-micronesia-in-china/</link>
				<comments>/mos-asia-pacific-node-representative-visits-the-ambassador-of-the-federated-states-of-micronesia-in-china/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 10:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[NEWS]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=630</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p><img class="alignnone size-medium" src="http://www.mosdao.io/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/photo_2019-09-27_09-13-52.jpg" width="1280" height="852" /></p>
<p>On the afternoon of September 28th, Mr. Thomas, the representative of the MOS Asia Pacific node, visited the Embassy of the Federated States of Micronesia (hereinafter referred to as the “Federal Union”) in Beijing. Ambassador Carlson D. Apis, Ambassador of the Federal Embassy in China, met with Mr. Thomas and his party. The two sides held talks on promoting MOS and Micronesia blockchain financial infrastructure.</p>
<p>At the symposium, Lord Carl Appis expressed his gratitude to the MOS team for providing the opportunity to provide blockchain technical training to the students of the Federal Republic. He said: &#8220;I have been paying attention to the blockchain field for 2 years. Blockchain technology is an Internet-based distributed ledger technology with decentralization, high security, low credit cost, inability to tamper with and transparency. It provides a new credit creation mechanism and has broad application prospects in the financial field. The secret federation attaches great importance to blockchain technology. We believe that the blockchain will not even have a subversive effect on the financial industry. Bring a huge impact.&#8221;</p>
<p>His Excellency Carl Appis gave a positive assessment of MOS&#8217;s contribution to the financial industry. The Federal Embassy in China will fully support the MOS project and cooperate with Micronesia and Micronesia. Lord Carl Apis pointed out that Micronesia College is the only university in the United States, shouldering the heavy responsibility of cultivating national talents and supporting the development of national industries. MOS is the builder of global financial infrastructure. And sincerely invite the MOS team to visit Micronesia.</p>
<p>Mr. Thomas, the representative of the MOS Asia Pacific node, thanked Carl Apis for his active matchmaking and promoted the cooperation between MOS and Micronesia. He said that MOS is a new generation of blockchain financial infrastructure based on DAO2.0. It is recommended that both parties can cooperate as soon as possible, and sincerely invites Lord Carl Apis and the President of Micronesia to visit MOS to learn about The situation of disciplines and industrial development is conducive to enhancing mutual understanding and solidifying the foundation of cooperation.</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>/mos-asia-pacific-node-representative-visits-the-ambassador-of-the-federated-states-of-micronesia-in-china/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>MOS Starlight plans to enter the Embassy of Nigeria</title>
		<link>/mos-starlight-plans-to-enter-the-embassy-of-nigeria/</link>
				<comments>/mos-starlight-plans-to-enter-the-embassy-of-nigeria/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 10:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[NEWS]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=623</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p><img class="alignnone size-medium" src="http://www.mosdao.io/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/photo_2019-10-09_16-08-29-1.jpg" width="1280" height="853" /></p>
<p>Recently, MOS Asia Pacific node representative Mr. Thomas visited Ahmad Jidda, Ambassador of the Embassy of Nigeria to China, on the theme of “Leading new ideas in blockchain technology and collaborating on new financial ecology”. Blockchain financial technology has been discussed in depth in a series of issues such as banking applications and technological innovations. Ahmad Jidda, the ambassador to China, expressed his strong interest in the MOS project. Optimistic about the future development of the MOS project, affirming the direction of the MOS project in the blockchain finance field, the future may bring more opportunities for cooperation and development opportunities for both parties.</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>/mos-starlight-plans-to-enter-the-embassy-of-nigeria/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>MOS Starlight plans to enter the Embassy of Malta</title>
		<link>/mos-starlight-plans-to-enter-the-embassy-of-malta/</link>
				<comments>/mos-starlight-plans-to-enter-the-embassy-of-malta/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2019 08:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[NEWS]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=611</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="vc_row wpb_row vc_row-fluid"><div class="wpb_column vc_column_container vc_col-sm-12"><div class="vc_column-inner"><div class="wpb_wrapper">
	<div class="wpb_text_column wpb_content_element " >
		<div class="wpb_wrapper">
			<p><img class="alignnone size-medium" src="/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/photo_2019-09-27_09-19-38.jpg" width="1280" height="852" /></p>
<p>Mr. Thomas, the representative of the MOS Asia Pacific node, had a cordial talk with the Ambassador of the Republic of Malta to China, Mr. John Aquilina, and made an in-depth study on the “global blockchain financial self-organizing ecosystem”. Mr. John Aquilina confirmed He also praised the MOS project&#8217;s professionalism and achievements in the blockchain finance field, and also comprehensively introduced the advantages of Malta. Malta is the first country to issue clear legislation and guidelines for the industry, taking the lead in the regulation of cryptocurrency and blockchain technology. The habitat of the world&#8217;s leading financial companies. Mr. Thomas, through the MOS Asia Pacific node representative, expressed his sincere sincerity to Malta for the MOS project. Mr. Thomas also strongly agrees: &#8220;The MOS project is simultaneously connecting with countries with multiple blockchain financial technologies open to the world. From the standpoint of cryptocurrency and financial technology, Malta is very advanced. I will convey this to the MOS team. The MOS team was impressed with the clear and forward-thinking thinking of the future.</p>

		</div>
	</div>
</div></div></div></div>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>/mos-starlight-plans-to-enter-the-embassy-of-malta/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
